Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - September 27, 1978: Phyllis Bruce, Soprano, performed by Phyllis Bruce, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - September 30, 1978: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 3)
    - October 1, 1978: Music at the Honors College, performed by Andrew Spearman, Edward Foster, George Barth, James Jacobs, Emery Tapley, Michael Thomson (Box 3)
    - October 2, 1978: A Concert of Bharata Natyam, performed by Lakshmi Shanmukham, daughter of Balasaraswati; et al. (Box 3)
    - October 19, 1978: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 3)
    - October 22, 1978: Instrument Music of the French Baroque, performed by Adrianne Greenbaum, Grace Feldman, Britt Wheeler (Box 3)
    - October 22, 1978: Choral Music of Eighteenth-Century France, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - October 27, 1978: An Evening of Classical Japanese Music & Dance, performed by Karo Yamahiko VI, Chie Yamahiko, Yachiyo Hatta, Namino Torii (Box 3)
    - October 28, 1978: Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - November 3, 1978: Morton Feldman and Soloists, performed by Morton Feldman, Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 4, 1978: Javanese Wayang Kulit, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - November 7, 1978: Neely Bruce, Composer/Pianist, performed by Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - November 10-11, 1978: Uptown, Downtown, performed by Mark Slobin, John Basinger, et al. (Box 3)
    - November 17, 1978: Handel's Opera Acis and Galatea, performed by New York Chamber Soloists (Box 3)
    - December 1, 1978: An Evening of West African Music and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah and his students, et al. (Box 3)
    - December 2, 1978: Wesleyan University Orchestra with Wesleyan Singers, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Wesleyan Singers, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - December 3, 1978: Music at the Honors College, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - December 5, 1978: The New England String Quartet, performed by Theodore Arm, Ik-Hwan Bae, Robert Coleman, Mary Lou Rylands, guest artists (Box 3)
    - December 6, 1978: The Wesleyan University Wind Ensemble, performed by Thomas Ridenour (Box 3)
    - December 7, 1978: Mary Bon, Organist, performed by Mary Bon (Box 3)
    - December 8, 1978: Wesleyan Big Band in Concert, performed by Wesleyan Big Band, Bill Lowe (Box 3)
    - December 9-10, 1978: Candlelight Concert, performed by The Concert Choir of Wesleyan University, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - December 12, 1978: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Bradford Wells, Beth Solowey (Box 3)
    - January 21, 1979: Music of Ferruccio Busoni, performed by Peter Armstrong (Box 3)
    - January 24, 1979: Nrityarpana, performed by Ritha Devi (Box 3)
    - January 26, 1979: Richard Stoltzman, Clarinet; Bill Douglas, Bassoon and Piano, performed by Richard Stoltzman, Bill Douglas (Box 3)
    - February 2, 1979: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 3)
    - February 3, 1979: The Unaccompanied Flute, performed by Julie Scolnik (Box 3)
    - February 4, 1979: Music at the Honors College, performed by Helen Huybrechts, Peter Sacco, Harry Clark (Box 3)
    - February 6, 1979: Piano Music of William Duckworth, performed by Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - February 9, 1979: Recent Music of Alvin Lucier, performed by Alvin Lucier, Nicolas Collins (Box 3)
    - February 12, 1979: The Watts Electric Company, performed by Satoru Shimazaki, John Watts, Jonathan Mink (Box 3)
    - February 13, 1979: Teresa Escandon, Pianist, performed by Teresa Escandon (Box 3)
    - February 16, 1979: Honors Thesis: A Recital of Songs, performed by Guy F. Pugh, George Barth (Box 3)
    - February 17, 1979: Concert of Bharata Natyam, performed by Kay Poursine, et al. (Box 3)
    - February 18, 1979: The Dawn of the Post-Disco Age, performed by Stephanie Woodard, Ellen Webb, Peter Zummo, Bill Ruyle (Box 3)
    - February 23, 1979: Sankyoku, performed by Namino Torii, Reihi Sano, guest artists (Box 3)
    - February 24, 1979: Wesleyan University Orchestra with the Concert Choir, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Concert Choir, Roger Colie, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 1, 1979: Milton Sutter, Organist, performed by Milton Sutter (Box 3)
    - March 2, 1979: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Trichy Sankaran (Box 3)
    - March 3, 1979: Phillip de Fremer, Guitar, performed by Phillip de Fremery (Box 3)
    - March 4, 1979: Music at the Honors College, performed by Naomi Amos (Box 3)
    - March 6, 1979: A Choral Miscellany, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - March 28, 1979: Yakshagana: Ritual Dance and Drama from South India, performed by Unknown (Box 3)
    - March 31, 1979: The Wesleyan Woodwind Quintet, performed by The Wesleyan Woodwind Quintet, assisting artists (Box 3)
    - April 1, 1979: A Struggle for Women's Sufferage, A History in Song, performed by R. Elizabeth Sanders, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 3, 1979: Britt Wheeler, Organist, performed by Britt Wheeler (Box 3)
    - April 6, 1979: New Hungarian Quartet, performed by Andor Toth; Richard Young; Denes Koromzay; Andor Toth, Jr. (Box 3)
    - April 7, 1979: Sankyoku Onshukai, performed by The students of Namino Torii and Reihi Sano (Box 3)
    - April 8, 1979: The Honors College and the Department of Music Present, performed by Eliot T. Bailen, Elizabeth Sawyer (Box 3)
    - April 9-10, 1979: Dido and Aeneas, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 16, 1979: New Music/Video, performed by Stephanie Koplowitz (Box 3)
    - April 20, 1979: Senior Recital, performed by Ken Wessel (Box 3)
    - April 21, 1979: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 3)
    - April 23, 1979: Recital of Works for Flute and Piano, and Piano Solo, performed by Peter Standaart, Lynn Crigler (Box 3)
    - April 24, 1979: Wesleyan Big Band, performed by Wesleyan Big Band, Bill Barron, Bill Dargan (Box 3)
    - April 27, 1979: An Evening of Javanese Dance and Music, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - April 28-29, 1979: The Concert Choir, performed by The Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 29, 1979: A Sting Quartet Recital, performed by Mary Ross, David Rowe, Greg Andris, Peter Brooks (Box 3)
    - May 1, 1979: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Bradford Wells, Beth Solowey (Box 3)
    - May 5, 1979: Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - May 6, 1979: An Evening of West African Music and Dance, performed by Freeman Donkor and his students, guest artists (Box 3)
    - May 6, 1979: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 7, 1979: A Concert of New Music from the Black Religious Experience, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 7, 1979: Bugaku: An Evening of Japanese Court Dance, performed by Masataro Togi and his students, Suenobu Togi (Box 3)
    - May 12, 1979: Traditional Dance and Music of Bali, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - September 18, 1979: An Evening with Carrie Jacobs-Bond, performed by Phyllis Bruce, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - September 21-26, 1979: Navaratri Celebration, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - September 22, 1979: An Evening's Dance Recital, performed by Maya Kulkarini (Box 3)
    - September 23, 1979: A Program of Baroque Music, performed by Grace Feldman, Peter Standaart, Britt Wheeler (Box 3)
    - September 23, 1979: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Jon B. Higgins, Joseph Cormack, T. Viswanathan, T. Ranganathan (Box 3)
    - September 24, 1979: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Karaikudi S. Subramanian, Douglas Knight, Tanjore Ranganathan (Box 3)
    - September 25, 1979: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, Woodman Taylor, Trichy Sankaran (Box 3)
    - September 29, 1979: Frances Burnett, Pianist, performed by Frances Burnett (Box 3)
    - October 16, 1979: John Riddle, Organist, performed by John Riddle (Box 3)
    - October 19, 1979: New Music for Chorus, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - October 19, 1979: Lecture-Recital: Interpreting New Music, performed by James Fulkerson (Box 3)
    - October 20, 1979: James Fulkerson, Trombonist, performed by James Fulkerson (Box 3)
    - October 21, 1979: Nameless, performed by Peter Stempe, Edwin Lawrence, Garrett Bennett (Box 3)
    - October 28, 1979: Music at the Honors College, performed by Carver Blanchard, George Hummel (Box 3)
    - November 2, 1979: Piedmont Chamber Players, performed by Piedmont Chamber Players (Box 3)
    - November 3, 1979: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - November 6, 1979: John Cage Song Books, performed by Neely Bruce, David Barron, Phyllis Bruce, Marc Grafe (Box 3)
    - November 9, 1979: Recital of Flute Ensemble Music, performed by Chris Abajian, Cindy Clark, Karen Van Dyck, Peter Standaart (Box 3)
    - November 11, 1979: Frederick Martell Black, Tenor, performed by Frederick Martell Black, Naomi Amos, Phyllis Bruce, William Myers (Box 3)
    - November 13, 1979: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 3)
    - November 16, 1979: Concord String Quartet, performed by Mark Sokol, Andrew Jennings, John Kochanowski, Norman Fischer (Box 3)
    - November 28, 1979: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 3)
    - November 29, 1979: An Evening of Turkish Mystic and Classic Music, performed by Collins Lein, Bob Labaree, Michele Shallon, et al. (Box 3)
    - December 2, 1979: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - December 7, 1979: An Evening of West African Music and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman Donkor, Yaa Johnson, Tackie Ofori (Box 3)
    - December 9, 1979: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - December 11, 1979: Somewhat New Music, performed by Eric Ranvig, et al. (Box 3)
    - December 11, 1979: Chamber Music Recital, performed by Wendy Kosakoff, David Rowe, Greg Andris, Hugh Judge, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - December 13, 1979: The Waverly Consort, performed by Machael Jaffee (Box 3)
    - January 27, 1980: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 3)
    - February 8, 1980: Ursula Oppens, Piano, performed by Ursula Oppens (Box 3)
    - February 9, 1980: The Wesleyan Woodwind Quintet, performed by Peter Standaart, Peter Stempe, Thomas Ridenour, Andrew Spearman, Garrett Bennett (Box 3)
    - February 15, 1980: The Da Capo Chamber Players, performed by Andre Emelianoff, Laura Flax, Joel Lester, Patricia Spencer, Joan Tower (Box 3)
    - February 16, 1980: The Harvard-Radcliffe Collegium Musicum, performed by Jameson Marvin, Vincent Paul Moravec (Box 3)
    - February 17, 1980: A Recital, performed by Adam Dydak (Box 3)
    - February 17, 1980: Chinese Music Concert, performed by Chang Ch'ung-ho (Box 3)
    - February 19, 1980: Violin/Cello Recital, performed by Peter Sacco, Harry Clark (Box 3)
    - February 22, 1980: A Concert of Experimental Music, performed by Paul De Marinis, Alvin Lucier, John Bischoff (Box 3)
    - February 26, 1980: All Bach Harpsichord Recital with Commentary: Paul Maynard, performed by Paul Maynard (Box 3)
    - February 27, 1980: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 3)
    - March 1, 1980: Julie Scolnik, Flute; Cheung Wai Lang, Piano, performed by Julie Scolnik, Cheung Wai Lang (Box 3)
    - March 2, 1980: Naomi Amos, Piano, performed by Naomi Amos (Box 3)
    - March 4, 1980: David Barron, Bass-Baritone; Neely Bruce, Pianist, performed by David Barron, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - March 7, 1980: A Concert of Karnatak Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, T. Ranganathan (Box 3)
    - March 8, 1980: Orchestra, performed by Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - March 9, 1980: Senior Vocal Recital, performed by Gregory Neal Brown, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - March 9, 1980: Recital Music for Clarinet, performed by Thomas Ridenour, et al. (Box 3)
    - March 12, 1980: Carol Beth Choate, Organist, performed by Carol Beth Choate (Box 3)
    - April 2, 1980: A Concert of Contemporary Music for Solo Violin, performed by Malcolm Goldstein (Box 3)
    - April 8, 1980: Traditional and Contemporary Japanese Music, performed by Reiko Kamata, Keiko Kanogawa, Ralph Samuelson (Box 3)
    - April 11, 1980: Benjamin Luxton, Baritone; Yehudi Wyner, Piano, performed by Benjamin Luxton, Yehudi Wyner (Box 3)
    - April 12, 1980: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band (Box 3)
    - April 18, 1980: A Concert of Bharata Natyam, performed by Kay Poursine, et al. (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1980: Choral Music of the Masters, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - April 19, 1980: Senior Recital, performed by Tami Bauer (Box 3)
    - April 20, 1980: Gregory and Geofrey Bonenberger, Classical Guitarists, performed by Gregory Bonenberger, Geofrey Bonenberger (Box 3)
    - April 26, 1980: Katherine Bergeron, Flute, performed by Katherine Bergeron, George Barth, Winifred Kerner, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - May 3, 1980: A Piano Recital, performed by Terri Seligman (Box 3)
    - May 4, 1980: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 6, 1980: Senior Thesis Piano Recital, performed by Beth Yergin (Box 3)
    - May 9, 1980: Talking Drums, performed by Arbraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman K. Donkor (Box 3)
    - May 10, 1980: Four Saints in Three Acts, performed by The Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 3)
    - May 11, 1980: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 3)
    - May 11, 1980: Pianists on Parade, performed by Various (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1980: Wesleyan University Department of Music Presents, performed by Hugh Judge, Andrew Alter, Joanne Lee (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1980: Britt Wheeler, Organist, performed by Britt Wheeler (Box 3)
    - May 13, 1980: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Jonathan McCord, Paul Harcourt, Bradford Wells (Box 3)
    - May 14, 1980: Banning Eyre, Guitar, performed by Banning Eyre (Box 3)
    - May 16, 1980: Music for the Clarinet, performed by Tom Hilton (Box 3)
    - May 18, 1980: Senior Piano Recital, performed by Jodi Gelfand (Box 3)
    - September 14, 1980: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldman (Box 4)
    - September 18, 1980: Agustin Anievas, Piano, performed by Aguistin Anievas (Box 4)
    - September 20, 1980: Flute Recital, performed by Peter Standaart, Peter Armstrong, Britt Wheeler (Box 4)
    - September 28, 1980: Duo Piano Recital, performed by Naomi Amos, George Barth (Box 4)
    - October 1, 1980: Charles Krigbaum, Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 4)
    - October 4, 1980: Flute and Guitar, performed by Rie Schmidt, Benjamin Verdery (Box 4)
    - October 17, 1980: Eliot Fisk, Guitar, performed by Eliot Fisk (Box 4)
    - October 19, 1980: Music at the Honors College, performed by Claudia Ayer, Naomi Amos (Box 4)
    - October 24, 1980: Jazz Ensemble, performed by Bill Barron, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Bill Lowe, Kenny Barron (Box 4)
    - October 26, 1980: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldman (Box 4)
    - November 1, 1980: The Wesleyan University Concert Choir and the Sylvan Consort with Instrumentalists, performed by The Wesleyan University Concert Choir, The Sylvan Consort, Richard Winslow, Sylvie Stewart, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 7, 1980: The Wesleyan University Orchestra Performs Mozart's Piano Concerto in A Major, K. 488, and Other Works, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie, Cheung Wai Lang (Box 4)
    - November 14, 1980: Concert Royal, New York Baroque Dance Company, performed by James Richman, Ann Jacoby, et al. (Box 4)
    - November 15, 1980: Ceremonial & Mystical Music Poetry Whirling, performed by Collins Lein, Friends (Box 4)
    - November 16, 1980: Irene Cervantes, Viola; Edwin Lawrence, Piano and Harpsichord; Thomas Ridenour, Clarinet, performed by Irene Cervantes, Edwin Lawrence, Thomas Ridenour (Box 4)
    - November 18, 1980: Music of Andre Jolivet, performed by The Wesleyan University Wind Quintet (Box 4)
    - November 21, 1980: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band (Box 4)
    - November 22, 1980: A Piano-Forte Recital, performed by Adam Dydak (Box 4)
    - November 23, 1980: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldman (Box 4)
    - November 24-25, 1980: Three Monologues for Actors and Musicians, performed by Bob Labaree, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 3, 1980: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 4)
    - December 5, 1980: Talking Drums: An Evening of West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman Donkor, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 7, 1980: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - December 9, 1980: Informal Student Organ Recital, performed by Paul Harcourt, Jonathan McCord (Box 4)
    - December 10, 1980: An Evening of Song (with a Touch of Theatre), performed by Sylvie Stewart, Camilla deLeon (Box 4)
    - December 10, 1980: Baroque Chamber Music, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - December 11, 1980: Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roger Solie (Box 4)
    - December 12, 1980: Bill Lowe: Black Music, performed by Bill Lowe, et al. (Box 4)
    - December 14, 1980: Candlelight Concert, performed by Wesleyan Concert Choir, Richard Winslow (Box 4)
    - January 31, 1981: Jazz Ensemble Concert, performed by Bill Barron, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Bill Lowe, Kenny Barron (Box 4)
    - February 1, 1981: The Heller-Burnham Violin Duo, performed by Lesley Heller, James Burnham, Mary Louise Vetrano (Box 4)
    - February 3, 1981: Jazz and World Music Songs, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - February 8, 1981: The Art of Stillness: Piano Music of Erik Satie, performed by Adam Dydak (Box 4)
    - February 13, 1981: Experimental Music, performed by David Behrman, Paul de Marinis, Alvin Lucier, Sumarsam, T. Viswanathan (Box 4)
    - February 15, 1981: Chinese New Year's Concert, performed by Tong Kin-woon, Alan Thrasher, Chen Shui-wan, et al. (Box 4)
    - February 21, 1981: Choral Music of the Masters, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Naomi Amos (Box 4)
    - February 24, 1981: Neil Keen, Organist, performed by Neil Keen (Box 4)
    - February 27, 1981: Beaux Arts Trio, performed by Menahem Pressler, Isidore Cohen, Bernard Greenhouse (Box 4)
    - March 1, 1981: The Wesleyan University Concert Choir, performed by The Wesleyan University Concert Choir, Alison Neely, Adam Dydak, Britt Wheeler, Double Wind Quintet (Box 4)
    - March 1, 1981: Music at the Honors College, performed by George Barth, Jacqueline Ridenour, Peter Standaart (Box 4)
    - March 3, 1981: James G. Swisher, Pianist, performed by James G. Swisher (Box 4)
    - March 8, 1981: Megan Norris, Piano and Marimba; Andrew Alter, Piano; David Rowe, Violin, performed by Megan Norris, Andrew Alter, David Rowe (Box 4)
    - March 9, 1981: Senior Project Jazz Concert, performed by Greg Shatan (Box 4)
    - March 31, 1981: Benjamin Whitten, Pianist, performed by Benjamin Whitten (Box 4)
    - April 2, 1981: British Choral Music of the Renaissance and Twentieth Century, performed by Cambridge University Chamber Choir, Richard Marlow (Box 4)
    - April 3, 1981: South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, T. Ranganathan (Box 4)
    - April 4, 1981: New Music for Singers in Groups, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Naomi Amos (Box 4)
    - April 6, 1981: Roots to Fruits, performed by Joe Galeota, Robert Levin (Box 4)
    - April 10, 1981: Perfect Lives (Private Parts), performed by Robert Ashley, et al. (Box 4)
    - April 12, 1981: Messiah: Parts Two and Three, performed by Wesleyan University Concert Choir, Richard Winslow (Box 4)
    - April 13, 1981: Topeng Babakan, performed by Marjie Suanda, Endo Suanda (Box 4)
    - April 14, 1981: Music of Five Continents, performed by Bill Cole, Farel Johnson (Box 4)
    - April 16, 1981: Senior Recital, performed by Tom Hilton, Andrew Alter, Andrea Spenser (Box 4)
    - April 18, 1981: Music for Oboe, Piano, performed by Teresa Anna Kosciuk, Alison Patricia Williams, Alison G. Neely (Box 4)
    - April 19, 1981: A Violin and Viola Recital, performed by Wendy Kosakoff, Greg Andris, et al. (Box 4)
    - April 21, 1981: An Evening of Iroquois Social Dances, performed by Avery Jimerson, Fidelia Jimerson, et al. (Box 4)
    - April 21, 1981: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, Bill Baron (Box 4)
    - April 24, 1981: Javanese Music and Dance, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan, Sumarsam, R. M. Soekanto, S. Darsono, Urip Sri Maeny (Box 4)
    - April 25, 1981: Little Big Band Concert, performed by Steve Ritz, et al. (Box 4)
    - April 26, 1981: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - April 29, 1981: Victorian Songs for Every Taste, performed by Phyllis Hurt, Dennis Michael Davis, Richard Cohn, Nicholas Temperley (Box 4)
    - May 2, 1981: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Roy Wiseman (Box 4)
    - May 3, 1981: Piano Recital, performed by Joanne M. Lee (Box 4)
    - May 4, 1981: An Evening of Balinese Dance, performed by I Wayan Dibia, Ni Made Wiratini Dibia, Desak Nyoman Suarthi (Box 4)
    - May 5, 1981: Wesleyan Flute Ensemble Recital, performed by Wesleyan Flute Ensemble (Box 4)
    - May 6, 1981: Britt Wheeler, Organ, performed by Britt Wheeler, Peter Brooks (Box 4)
    - May 6, 1981: Senior Oboe Recital, performed by Joseph Siegel, Donald Berman (Box 4)
    - Undated: Spring Concert, performed by Bryant Urban, et al. (Box 4)
    - May 8, 1981: Talking Drums, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman Donkor, et al. (Box 4)
    - May 9, 1981: Senior Piano Recital, performed by Diane Goldstein (Box 4)
    - Undated: Wesleyan University Department of Music Presents, performed by Paul Halliday, Wenday Kosakoff, Greg Andris, Hugh Judge, Neely Bruce (Box 4)
    - May 10, 1981: Piano Recital, performed by Alison Neely (Box 4)
    - May 10, 1981: Senior Oboe Recital, performed by Joseph Siegel, Donald Berman (Box 4)
    - May 11, 1981: Javanese Wayang Kulit, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan, R. M. Sukanto, S. Darsono (Box 4)
    - May 12, 1981: Carver Blanchard, Lute/Guitar, performed by Carver Blanchard, Naomi Amos, Peter Standaart (Box 4)
    - May 15, 1981: Arnold's Orchestra of Excited Strings with Special Guest Pipes Presents "Nodal Excitation", performed by Arnold Dreyblatt, et al. (Box 4)
    - May 16, 1981: Baroque Chamber Music, performed by Students of Britt Wheeler (Box 4)
    - May 16, 1981: Piano Recital, performed by Rebecca Brown (Box 4)
    - July 12, 1981: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by Various (Box 4)
    - September 11, 1981: Robert Briggs, Bass-Baritone, performed by Robert Briggs, Kenneth Merrill (Box 4)
    - September 18, 1981: Benjamin Verdery, Classical Guitarist, performed by Benjamin Verdery (Box 4)
    - September 19, 1981: A Gala Concert of Nineteenth-Century Vocal Chamber Music by American Composers, performed by Neely Bruce, et al. (Box 4)
    - September 22, 1981: A Concert of Baharata Natam, performed by Lakshmi Shanmukham, daughter of Balasaraswati (Box 4)
    - October 1-2, 1981: The Concord String Quartet, performed by Mark Sokol, Andrew Jenninga, John Kochanowski, Norman Fischer (Box 4)
    - October 4, 1981: Anthony Tommasini, Piano, performed by Anthony Tommasini (Box 4)